

# **DONG BICH THUC NU**

**DEVELOPER** 



I have 2+ years of experience working on real-world projects, in both backend and frontend roles.
I am always up-to-date with the latest technologies and passionate about learning and applying them to bring value to customers and users.

Confident in my communication skills, I combine creativity and passion to continuously learn and contribute effectively to any project.

Good English communication (Toeic 670)

# Work experience

Jan 2024 - Nov 2024

Airplan service project

**Backend Developer at FPT** 

In the Japanese airline project, I developed APIs to support flight ticket booking and the booking of services for ANA Airline, as well as assisting with the project during the go-live phase.

#### Technologies used

Lowcode (MuleSoft): Anypoint Platform, Anypoint Studio, Dataweave

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023

**Product Management Project** 

Java Developer at FPT

In the product management project for a chain of stores, I worked as a backend developer, designing APIs to manage products and ensure data synchronization.

#### Technologies used

Spring Framework, MySQL

Feb 2023 - May 2023

**Employee Management Project** 



**Phone** 

0845848284



Email thucnu0608@gmail.com



Dob

06/08/2001





**Address**Can Tho, Vietnam



Gender





Website

Github:https://github.com/thucnu
Portfolio:https://vercel.com/thucnu/portfolio



#### **Education**

Can Tho University | 09/2019 - 09/2023

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 3.34/4.00

Certificate of Excellent Student for academic years 2020-2021 and 2021-2022.

Scholarship for good students in the second semester of the academic year 2019-2020, excellent students in the academic year 2020-2021, and academic year 2021-2022.

Academic exchange at the Research and Development Faculty, Royal University of Phnom Penh (RUPP), Cambodia in 2022.



### **Certifications**

Dec 2024

Mendix rapid developer

Jun 2024

ML practitioner certificate

May 2024

Advanced designer certification

Apr 2024

#### Frontend Developer at NFQ

That project has been designed from the ground up to make career progression and personal growth fun and engaging through gamification and tangible rewards. It is built to enhance or even replace the usual cycle of performance reviews.

#### **Technologies used**

Vuejs, Typescript, Naive UI, TailwindCSS

Jan 2022 - May 2023

#### **DoctorCare**

#### **Personal Project**

A website that supports users in scheduling medical appointments online without the need to physically go to the clinic and wait for a queue number.

#### **Technologies used**

Reactjs, Nodejs, Postgresql, Bootstrap 4

Oracle cloud infrastructure for sunbird ed specialty



## **Skills**

ReactJS Java

JavaScript Spring Framework

TypeScript MuleSoft
Naive UI Mendix
TailwindCSS MySQL

Bootstrap 4 PostgreSQL

Github English (Toeic 670)

© topcv.vn